webmasterradio.fm 2018-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Webmaster Radio

### Privacy Policy

**Overview**  
NextGen Media, LLC. ("WebmasterRadio.FM") is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. WEBMASTER RADIO strives to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the WEBMASTER RADIO. By using WEBMASTER RADIO, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement, do not use the WEBMASTER RADIO.

WEBMASTER RADIO may contain links to web sites of both our affiliated and non-affiliated entities, including access to content, products and services of such affiliated and non-affiliated entities, over which WEBMASTER RADIO has no control ("other sites"). In some cases, these other sites may have the same (or a similar) look and feel as our Site and therefore may appear to be part of WEBMASTER RADIO. WEBMASTER RADIO is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from WEBMASTER RADIO. WEBMASTER RADIO encourages you to review the privacy policies of these other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the Information (as defined below in the paragraph titled "Collection and Retention of Information") collected on WEBMASTER RADIO and does not apply to information WEBMASTER RADIO collects in any other fashion.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us via this site or using the contact information provided below.

**Collection and Retention of Information  
** In some areas, WEBMASTER RADIO requests or may request that you provide personal information which may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible ("Personal Information"). Unless you provide it to us voluntarily, WEBMASTER RADIO does not collect Personal Information about you. WEBMASTER RADIO gathers or may gather certain information about your use of WEBMASTER RADIO (such as what areas you visit and what services you access) and information about your computer hardware and software, including without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web Site addresses ("Usage Information", "Non-Personal Information"). The Personal Information and Non-Personal Information we collect and/or that you voluntarily provide on the Site will be referred to in this Privacy Statement collectively as "Information."

Remember, WEBMASTER RADIO is intended to promote your visibility online and great care should be taken when deciding whether to provide information, and that if you provide any of your Personal Information to WEBMASTER RADIO for posting in areas of the Site, it may be publicly viewed or viewed by registered members of the Site. Such Personal Information may be collected and used by others over whom WEBMASTER RADIO has no control. Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Statement, WEBMASTER RADIO is not responsible for the use made by third parties of Information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of the Site.

You can correct or update your WEBMASTER RADIO account profile at any time. Moreover, you can delete your contact and personal information from our online database or close your WEBMASTER RADIO account at any time by contacting us here, in which event WEBMASTER RADIO will remove all copies of your Personal Information and your WEBMASTER RADIO SITE account profile information.

**Use of Information by WEBMASTER RADIO**  
WEBMASTER RADIO uses the Information gathered on the WEBMASTER RADIO, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the Site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering our products and services to you.  
WEBMASTER RADIO may use your Personal Information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the Site, such as new WEBMASTER RADIO SITE opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the Personal Information you have provided to us. In addition, at the time of registration for WEBMASTER RADIO, you have the option to elect to receive additional communications, information and promotions including, without limitation, free informational newsletters from WEBMASTER RADIO relating to topics that may be of special interest to you.

**Children**  
WEBMASTER RADIO is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered or is attempting to register on the Site, we will notify the user that he or she is not eligible for registration. We will then delete any related Personal Information from our records.

**User Feedback**  
WEBMASTER RADIO is pleased to hear from users and welcomes your comments regarding the Site in our feedback area of the Site. Please be advised, however, that WEBMASTER RADIO and its employees do not accept or consider unsolicited ideas, including ideas for new products or technologies, processes, materials, marketing plans, or new product names. Please do not send your unsolicited ideas or any original materials to WEBMASTER RADIO or anyone at the WEBMASTER RADIO STUDIOS. If, despite this request, you still send WEBMASTER RADIO your ideas and original materials, please understand that by submitting such information through this Site, you assign WEBMASTER RADIO, free of charge, all worldwide rights, title and interest in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the information or materials you submit. We will be entitled to use any such information and materials for any purpose whatsoever without restriction and without compensating you in any way, and by submitting any such information and materials, you represent to WEBMASTER RADIO that you have the right to do so.

**Disclosure of Information to Others**  
WEBMASTER RADIO does not disclose to third parties your Personal Information, except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs.

WEBMASTER RADIO may disclose such Personal Information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you provide any of your Personal Information to WEBMASTER RADIO for posting in areas of the Site that may be publicly viewed or viewed by registered members of the Site, WEBMASTER RADIO will disclose your Personal Information to third parties who conduct searches on or through the Site or the WEBMASTER RADIO Services.

WEBMASTER RADIO may disclose your Personal Information to companies and individuals it employs to perform services on its behalf that are necessary for operation of the Site and the WEBMASTER RADIO Services, including hosting WEBMASTER RADIO's web servers, analyzing data, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. When we disclose your Personal Information to these persons, it is subject to agreements that require these companies and individuals to process your Personal Information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Statement and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

WEBMASTER RADIO may disclose your Personal Information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if WEBMASTER RADIO believes in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights, safety or property of WEBMASTER RADIO, its affiliates, service providers, WEBMASTER RADIO's users or the public, or (c) prevent a crime or protect national security.

WEBMASTER RADIO may disclose and transfer your Personal Information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of WEBMASTER RADIO's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, liquidation, dissolution, consolidation or sale of all or a substantial portion of our business, trade or assets. In addition, in the event WEBMASTER RADIO becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, WEBMASTER RADIO or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of your Personal Information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. Subject to your election to opt out as described below, by using this Site, you consent to the sale and transfer of your Personal Information as described in this paragraph.

WEBMASTER RADIO may also share Non-Personal Information about Site visitors to its clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors who visit our Site and how those visitors use the Site.

The Personal Information that you submit via this Site is stored on servers in the United States. The storage on servers in the United States is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. If you are located in another jurisdiction, you should be aware that once your Personal Information is submitted, it will be transferred to our servers in the USA using secure encryption-based transmission services, and that the USA currently does not have uniform data protection laws in place.  
Subject to your opt-out choices and all of the provisions contained in this Privacy Statement, you hereby consent to the collection, processing and transfer by WEBMASTER RADIO of your Personal Information for the purposes described under this Privacy Statement, including but not limited to the transfer of such Personal Information between WEBMASTER RADIO and its third party service providers and affiliates in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Your consent to our right to transfer Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Statement includes consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to jurisdictions that may have different levels of privacy protection than that available to you under your local law.

**Use of Cookies**  
WEBMASTER RADIO uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience, and facilitate your time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

WEBMASTER RADIO, like many sites, uses cookies for a variety of reasons to enhance the user experience such as recognizing that your are logged in. For example, if you register for services, a cookie helps WEBMASTER RADIO to recall your specific Information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of WEBMASTER RADIO's use of cookies, WEBMASTER RADIO can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized Site experience. This means however that we do link personally identifiable information you submit while on our Site. When you return to the Site, the Information you previously provided can be retrieved with the use of cookies, so you can easily use the features that you customized. WEBMASTER RADIO also uses cookies to track click streams. Cookies are required to create and login to the Site.

**Updating Your Information**  
You may review, correct, update or change your Personal Information at any time. Simply log into your WEBMASTER RADIO account, review your account information and, if you wish, edit it with the options provided.

You may opt-out of receiving communications from WEBMASTER RADIO concerning other products or services available from WEBMASTER RADIO (except for communications necessary for your use of or our operation of the Site). If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by sending us a message through our contact page. In the event you opt-out, we may retain your e-mail address and share your email address with our third party service providers for the purpose of honoring your request to opt-out of receiving such communications from us or our third party service providers on our behalf.

**Security**  
WEBMASTER RADIO have implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures, reasonably appropriate to the nature of the data concerned, which are designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, WEBMASTER RADIO cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes.

When you place an order online at WEBMASTER RADIO, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted.

**Changes to Privacy Statement**  
We will post any material changes to this Privacy Statement at least thirty (30) days prior to the changes taking effect. If we do make material changes to this Privacy Statement that affect our treatment of your Personal Information, we will provide you with e-mail notice. After the changes take effect, all newly collected Personal Information will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Statement ("Revised Privacy Statement"). If at any time, you have questions or concerns about the WEBMASTER RADIO Privacy Statement, please feel free to contact WEBMASTER RADIO at our customer feedback form.

**Contact Information**  
NextGen Media, LLC, is an Arizona Limited Liability Company with its principal place of business at  **14300 N Northsight Blvd, Suite 101, Scottsdale AZ 85260  **and is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the Information gathered at the WEBMASTER RADIO.

WEBMASTER RADIO welcomes your comments concerning this Privacy Statement. If you have comments or questions concerning this Privacy Statement, please contact WEBMASTER RADIO by sending us a message through our contact page.

**Thank you for using our WEBMASTER RADIO.**

Your use of our WEBMASTER RADIO is subject to and contingent upon your agreement with our Terms of Service, which are hereby incorporated by reference.

Except as described in this notice, and subject to your choices, WEBMASTER RADIO will not use your Personal Information for any other purpose unless we first obtain your express authorization.

NextGen Media, LLC  
Attn: Legal  
14300 N Northsight Blvd, Suite 101  
Scottsdale, AZ  
954-309-5578
